The intel we got from Saunders indicates that Page has taken the President hostage
and is holding him in South Africa.
Page has been using a Saunders Global Security facility
as a front for his Unified Citizens terrorist group.
We dug up a paper trail leading us to believe that Page has been gathering tantalum and columbite
two materials that can used to develop weaponry.
We don't know what Page's end game is,
but we can assume that he is preparing something big.
We are deploying all our units to this location.
These mercs are well-trained
and the base will be strongly defended
so expect heavy resistance.
Our troops are at a disadvantage here
so we'll need to hit where it hurts, and fast.
This isn't a raid, it's a war.
Retrieve the President at all costs.