We've confirmed that Edward Page is in Antarctica
and we have him surrounded.
Vehicles, artillery, and infantry units are in position.
Our intel indicates that Page has developed a biochemical weapon of some kind
perhaps involving a genetically-modified strain of H5N1.
Anderson's experience dealing with Page during the Fallen Nation incident will prove useful on this mission.
And as a member of the AFTER team
he'll be able to assist when you encounter weapons of mass destruction.
This is a seek-and-destroy mission.
First priority is to locate and neutralize Page.
Whatever else happens
we need to eliminate him.